Technical Skills:

- Platforms: CW Automate, Solarwinds N-Central, Logic Monitor, Jira, Confluence, Chocolatey, PowerShell DSC, GitHub, OPSGenie, UniFi.
- Mapps: Excel, VSCode, Git, Kanban, Teams, OneDrive, SSH, Visio, Selenium.
- Languages: PowerShell, SQL, Python 3, Batch, APIs, XML, JSON, bash, MS Flow.
- **OSes:** Windows, Apple OS X, VMWare ESXi, Linux (Debian, CentOS), Unix.
- Microsoft: ACL, Active Directory, Group Policy, Azure AD, InTune, 365 Admin, Exchange, WSUS, DNS, DHCP.
- Linux: ACL, OpenVPN, Bind DNS, ISC DHCP, PowerShell Core, IPTables, TIG Stack (Telegraf/Influx/Grafana), NFS, Samba, Cron, firewalld, ZFS, Ansible, Apache.

Professional Overview:

Tony has excellent experience in general desktop and server administration, and a solid understanding of the PowerShell object pipeline and modular toolmaking. With these skills, he can build tools to improve productivity, integrate tools and platforms, develop and deploy production monitoring and telemetry, such as solutions for software deployment failures, or registry data aggregation.

Tony relies on his exceptional customer service skills to set himself apart from others in the engineering field. He is highly self-motivated and directed, and has a keen attention to detail. His proven analytical and problem-solving abilities afford him the adaptability required for dynamic, multi-tenant environments. He possesses good time management, with awareness of priorities and a return on invested time.

Tony is effective at reducing risk of changes and providing technical guidance to team members, both in-person and through technical writing. His aptitude for diagnostics comes from a talent for pattern recognition and a desire to minimize repeat issues through discovery of root causes and alternative methods.

Online Profiles:

github.com/tonypags

linkedin.com/in/tony-pagliaro-a2923337

Accomplishments:

- Architect and deploy new RMM solution requiring migration from existing platform with zero downtime for 200+ global customers with 10,000 endpoints.
- Developed toolset and scripts to ingest scheduling, contact, and configuration data from PSA and RMM
 platforms, automating email reminders and notifications in a scalable way, saving 15-20 man-hours weekly,
 and adding features for timezone support, and auto-correcting bad data using cross references.
- Developed a script which gathers information on new AD users from distributed networks across 200+ domains, which generated new business revenue of \$80-100k per month.
- Team leader of department with revenue measured in millions.

Work History:

Richard Fleischman and Associates, Inc.

New York, NY

Large MSP with private data center based in NY, with offices and colocations globally.

Senior Automation Engineer

July 2018 - Present

- Transform operational workflows into code: QA resource configs and deployments, bespoke automated emails.
- Maintain infrastructure of remote access and management platforms.
- Maintain PowerShell codebase and design proof of concepts in response to requests.
- Design procedures for Quality Assurance.
- Mentor DevOps engineer on use of PowerShell syntax, logic, objects, and modular functions, including DSC.

- Provide leadership guidance to team members during managerial transitions.
- Deploy custom data collection and aggregation across disparate networks and systems.
- Perform non-intrusive workstation diagnostics using CLI, SSH.
- Design service agent custom repair actions based on log parsing.
- Create software deployment template and procedure.
- Quickly design solutions for emergency use cases.

Applications Systems Administrator

April 2015 - June 2018

- Designed management solution for workstation maintenance by leveraging under-utilized RMM features.
- Built PowerShell solutions for custom interoperability between various platforms:
 - A scripted solution to aggregate disparate data sources for daily backup checks.
 - A tool for non-technical staff to export custom reports from a proprietary database.
 - Leveraged Selenium for automating a tedious web task, for which no APIs were available.
- Designed and implemented new policies for client on-/off-boarding.
- Created operational workflows for internal, day-to-day processes.
- Championed documentation of processes to allow for incremental improvement by automation.

Senior Field Technician

April 2012 - April 2015

- Hired to support newly created office for the investments division of a Fortune 200 company.
 - Acted as a liaison between HQ and investment office staff, executives, managers, traders, and vendors.
 - Created procedures for on-boarding c-suite team, directors, managers, staff, and other vendors.
 - Worked with HQ and/or vendors to coordinate on tele-presence, trading desk telephony, server and desktop support projects.
 - Authored documents for inventory of computers, printers, phone lines, and server and IT facility run books.
- Assigned to other high-value clients after demonstrating excellent client-service.

Domino Computing, Inc.

New York, NY

Small MSP supporting clients' technology in the NY tri-state area.

Senior Engineer

January 2011 – April 2012

- Handled service escalations, trained and supervised new hires.
- Performed changes to SonicWALL filter rules and VPN tunnels.

Engineer

October 2006 - January 2011

- Handled service requests via phone, remote access, and on-site visits.
- Maintained network systems and client documentation.
- Worked with chief officers, management, staff, and vendors.

Costas Kondylis & Partners LLP

New York, NY

High-end residential architecture firm, hired to assist IT Director.

Service Technician

June 2005 – October 2006

- Maintained Microsoft OS versions, AutoCAD, and large-format printers.
- Handled requests from c-suite, architects, and administrative staff.

Education:

University of Hartford 2000 – 2003

B.S. in Mechanical Engineering with a Concentration in Acoustics West Hartford, CT

Minor: Mathematics

Status: Graduated with Honors, May 2003 QPA: 3.5 / 4.0

University of New Haven 1998 – 2000
B.S. in Industrial Engineering West Haven, CT

Status: Transferred, May 2000

^{*}References available upon request

^{**}Phone number not publicly shared, please send email or LinkedIn message